What do you call scoring three or more goals by one person in a soccer game?
Foul.
Stand up!
Attention!
Yes, sir!
Please!
Good morning!
Today, I'd like to give you all
We have a common sense test for you today.
You have 15 minutes.
There are 30 questions in total.
I'll hand out the questions first.
I'm going to hand out the questions, and you're going to hold them, face down.
What do you mean, backwards?
It's like a test.
By the way, there should be nine of you.
But today, we have Hinano Sakura.
That's right!
I have common sense, so I'll be fine.
I want to take it the most!
A little more with your guess!
Put me in for a guess.
You have 15 minutes.
You will solve the problems.
After you finish solving the problems
We'll go over the answers one by one.
Yes, sir!
Then we'll give the wrong answer to the wrong person.
the answer to the wrong question
the answer to the wrong question.
Congratulations!
Is everyone ready?
Yes!
Let's go!
Let's start!
Yay!
The most Japanese
Europe.
What? What? That's hard!
What is that?
What is that? I don't get it!
What? It's hard!
What was this?
One more.
Mr. Teacher...
What? I don't get it!
What is it? No, I know what it is.
Oh, my God, look.
I'm in a hurry.
I can't write "impatient".
I don't know what this is.
What is it? Ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong.
What is it? What is it? Why won't it come out?
What? Wait, I don't know.
What? You know, sometimes you understand these things better in elementary school.
What? You know?
I knew more when I was in elementary school.
It's definitely different. Like this.
Oh, my God.
Definitely not.
What? I don't get it.
I don't get it.
You mean you don't know what this is?
Oh, no.
This is hard.
Come on in, you guys.
You're being selfish.
I can't.
Oh, no!
I didn't write my name down, so I'll be a Delten.
It's open!
I'm screwed.
Watch out, watch out, watch out!
That was close... really close...
It's over.
Please put the pen down.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
[fast forward]
Okay, now, let's start with the first question.
Don't have a writing flat, don't make one, don't let them bring it in.
Raise your hand if you got it wrong.
Phew!
What does it say?
Okay, from Ms. Tachibana.
I can't make it.
It's true, I can't make it.
I can't make it because you said you can't make it.
Because I can make it
I can't have it, I can't make it, I can't make it
Oh, yeah, right.
what has happened now?
next question
The full name of the current Prime Minister is
Wrong one
Masaki KanMasaki Suga
Ha-ha-ha!
I can give this one, um, one point in the gag round.
Question 2
The most sung song in the world is
The wrong one.
Yes
The two-eyed tortoise
A-ha-ha-ha
OH!
But you sing better than you sing
Good, that's great.
Question 4
The three greatest delicacies in the world are
Foie gras, caviar, and trifle.
The wrong one
Yes.
Habu, Hookworm, Anago
Heh.
Oh, can we eat these?
Chin and Yossan.
Oh, that way.
Chin and Josan.
Question 5.
The withholding scrutiny of food is
Sugar, salt, vinegar, soy sauce, miso
The wrong one
Yes, that way.
I'm tired of giving up
Yes, sir
Well, I wrote
I wrote "sugar, salt, vinegar, back fat, sauce".
Uh, back fat.
I couldn't think of any, so I wrote "back fat.
You sound confident that you're asking the right question.
Question 6
Weekly Jump
Yes.
Who is the main publisher?
Publisher of Weekly
The wrong one
Eh, yeah
No, that's too bad.
It says "Weekly Shonen Jump.
What?
It's exactly the same.
It's just as it should be.
Question 7
What is the sushi shop
purple is
How much is purple?
The answer is soy sauce.
The wrong one
Yes, you are.
In addition
Eggplant
It's purple, isn't it?
It's delicious, isn't it?
Checkout
Just a minute!
Purple, please.
Yes.
Purple.
Why do you say that?
Because it's Japanese.
Question 8
Astronaut Gagarin's maxim was
Earth was blue.
The wrong one
Fewer
The one that raises his hand
The sky was blue
Nice try.
You're right.
It's just like you said.
I don't care who you are.
I don't care if you don't want to go to space.
I don't care if you don't go to space.
It's purple.
Nope.
Wiper Man's Surprising
Question 9
What do you say when two people are in perfect synch?
Answer is
Breathing in unison
Shall we say this together?
Yes.
Breathing together.
Cute.
He's so cute.
He's so hot.
Breathing between two people
Question 10
Who lit the torch at the Tokyo Olympics?
I made a mistake.
The answer is Naomi Osaka.
The answer is
Kurisu SakihawaSakihawa Kurisu
That's hospitality!
That's great!
You did it!
I showed it to you.
It's fun!
It's the Olympics for sure, and it's fun.
It's embarrassing.
I think I'm going to do it.
Question 11.
That you get a big impact with a little head fat.
Catch a tie with a shrimp
If you get it wrong
It's too close.
Yes, sir.
Catch an adult with a kid.
That's hospitality!
Yay!
I made a mistake.
Scary.
I'm scared.
Question 12
Famous quotes from Rinma
Politics of the people by the people for the people
The wrong one
Politics for the people by Lucky's Happy
Politics all for himself
Question 13.
Correct answer.
Most Variable Player
I don't think anyone could guess this one.
I couldn't.
It's like a big one.
I see.
It's in Japanese.
It's like a big...
I don't know what to say anymore.
Music Victory President.
I think I've got something.
Guess the Most
Most Big
Cute!
Most Bee
Question 14.
Who came on this ship?
The answer is Perry
The wrong one
I really made a mistake.
Sakamoto Ryoma said he was watching.
Perry didn't show up.
Only the label showed up.
It's true.
It's not that I don't understand.
Question 15.
The prefectures in Kyushu, Okinawa, Fukuoka, and the other 6 prefectures are
Saga, Nagasaki, Kumamoto, Oita, Miyazaki, Kagoshima.
Kake.
But you got two questions right.
I guessed Saga and Nagasaki and wrote Watanabe prefecture.
Correct.
Interesting!
Question 16.
The four new sports for the Tokyo Olympics are
One is sport climbing, and the other three are
Karate, Skateboarding, Surfing
The wrong one
You'll never guess.
This one was wrong for all of us.
Dancing, jumping rope, pillow throwing.
Cute.
That's nice.
I wrote one and then I wrote taekwondo.
The same? What's that?
I love it.
I didn't think so when I first saw it.
Question 17
Shohei Otani's high school and baseball team are
Hanamaki-Higashi and Nippon Ham.
The wrong one.
I read everything wrong.
Miyagi in his hometown.
I could have read "baseball team", so I read "Rakuten".
Rakuten
I could read it normally
I wrote normally
Question 18
The name of the J-League team is
Vegalta Sendai.
The wrong one
I didn't know what the J. League was.
I wanted an explanation for that.
Anyway, it's a four-letter word.
It's like "Japan national team".
Japan Representative Sendai
Cool!
Explanation for the one that's out of reach
I didn't understand J-League
Question 19
How many years does FURUTO-ICHI occur once a year?
The answer is four years.The answer is four years.
Wrong one.
100 years
Poor Lissing.
Question 20.
Write the kanji with the most strokes you know.
I think it probably has the most.
There are definitely a lot of strokes.
27 strokes.
Wow!
What does that mean?
Q, Q, Q...
He could write so many kanji.
Let's just leave azuki as a circle.
That's great.
Question 21
How many seconds is time?
Correct answer is 3600 seconds.
Wrong.
I was going to write "6,000" but the person who put "0" by mistake is "Let me go.
Ah, 60,000,000
That's good. You'll make a lot of money.
That's a lot of money.
You better have a lot of time.
That's true.
I love it.
Question 22.
4 x 2 x 3 x 1 x 6 x 0 is
Hiroya
The answer is 0.
Those who got it wrong
Raise your hand.
Yes, I wrote 144.
I couldn't write 0 as usual, so I just calculated it and wrote 144.
I'm sorry.
Question 23
If you write "giku" in kanji, it means
Oh, this is scary!
I'm afraid of this one, too.
The wrong one
Yes ...
I made a mistake with "yi".
It's written in plain words, like "素は教徒符" or something
I see.
Almost everyone does.
Yes, I do.
But I love Gikuyu.
I'd definitely like to go there someday.
Question 24.
How do you write Saturday in English?
Thursday.
Oh, no!
Day is different.
What are you doing?
I can't write "Happy Birthday
Question 25.
Who wrote the Enge story?
Purple section
The wrong one
Who wrote
who
Question start
Question 26
The kanji for big beans is soybeans
Small beans are Watsuki, right?
Yes, sir.
The wrong one
Oh
Hey, hey, hey.
It says "small beans".
How do you read it?
Pats.
Question 27.
In 1600, the battle of Sekigahara took place at
Sekigahara.
Yes, sir.
The wrong one.
I wrote Kyoto.
Ah...
Yuna wrote Edo too.
Around Edo
Around Edo, please.
together please
Question 28.
What are the three major duties of citizens, the duty of education and the other two?
The correct answer is the duty to pay taxes and the duty to work.
The wrong one
The duty to take holidays and the duty to recreate.
Ah.
Strong.
It's an easy country.
The wrong one.
Certainly.
I don't need anything.
Important
Question 29.
What does HB stand for in a pencil?
The answer is hard black.
The wrong oneThe Wrong One
Black to use at home
Ahh.
Why are you talking Japanese?
Why the sudden Japanese?
You're right.
Last question
Question 30
What is it called when one person scores three or more goals in a soccer game?
The correct answer is a hat trick.
The wrong one.
I don't know.
Something's wrong.
The one who didn't get this right.
One at a time.
Bahr.
That's out.
You're out.
Genius.
That's good.
Genius
Unimaginative
Cool.
PK
too close to call
Mount
Genius
Lucky Bonus
what's that?
3 points
Too close to call
It's over.
That was long.
Question 4
Give yourself a total score at the very end.
One point?
All of them. One.
And finally, rank.
Please rank them.
It's not what I expected.
I'd like to be in the zone of decency.
In second place, with 16 points.
Mr. Hayano.
Oh, no.
What's the ranking?
If you are kind
Elite
Third place is
Actually tied for 4th place
12 points
This is
Mr. Kizuki and
Ms. Hazuki.
No, no, no.
Decent.
Fifth place, with 9 points...
Kitami
The sixth place and after are complicated.
The first place is
Shuka with 19 points
Finally, there are 6th, 7th and 8th place.
6th and 7th are tied with 5 points
The 8th place is 4 points
The first place winner
I'd like to announce the 6th and 7th place winners
Sixth and seventh place are...
Ms. Tachibana and Mr. Date.
Yes!
So that means...
Are you in? In here.
Oh, no.
The least Justic is the least Justic.
Kitami.
I have an image of him as a bit of a blabbermouth.
The image of a small person doing
Three mistakes.
It's totally up.
Seven points.
Ms. Kitami got 7 points for the lowest mistake.
She moved up to sixth place.
Billy is in a tie for second place.
Ms. Tachibana and Mr. Date have 5 points.
Thank you.
I'm not like that.
The King of Insanity.
whatever it is...
But if Hinomoto was here, he could have been a different person.
He has common sense, so he won't participate today
Absolutely
That boy is also the god of chinkaitou
Well, then, I'll do this one again, changing the question periodically.
Okay, so this is the first General Common Sense Test, and that's all.
Thank you very much.
If you enjoyed it, please give us a high rating!
That's all for us, the scar dust of Ishinomaki, Eginari and Suna.
Thank you very much!
Bye bye!